[Music]
do
good morning it is a rainy spring day
and the cherry trees are in full bloom
they're stunning and i simply had to go
and see them and take a couple branches
to decorate my home
[Music]
do
today i wanted to give you a little tour
of the lower level of my cottage
as it is finally complete and no doubt
you'll be able to follow my journey of
continually transforming the space over
the next several months
[Music]
it has been a very rainy day and the
last several weeks have been so cold and
for the most part overcast so it's been
a very slow coming of late spring and
it's hard to believe that soon it's
going to get quite warm
so i'm enjoying this era of
chilly mornings and cozy evenings in the
cottage with the
furnace still on which is kind of crazy
this time of year now the cottage is
complete
from a
physical standpoint as in
it has been renovated finally the
staircase is in
the showers are finally
done and plumbing and electricity is all
done so it is officially complete but
there still needs to be a lot of little
things done around the house to make it
feel
like the home space i have in my mind so
we are still in great need of a couch or
somewhere that we can sit in the
evenings which is really nice we
currently do not have anything like that
we still don't have wi-fi there's little
things we're working on but you know
we'll get there eventually if you stay
tuned for the next several months you
will see updates as i start to finalize
every room and finish painting which is
definitely my soul song when it comes to
creating a home space i'm just going to
pop in here
really quick because i forgot to say
that i have a little
uh fairy living inside my heart that
definitely likes to express herself in
her home space
and so it reflects a lot of what i
love
and
yeah i am incredibly lucky to be
marrying a man who
embraces
this side of me and has encouraged me to
personalize the space and let the little
fairy princess in my heart
speak out
and express herself so
sending you my love
and i hope you enjoy
[Music]
to prepare this home for you i did need
to get a few things done
even though i'm still settling in
painting on the walls always makes me
feel like i am where i'm meant to be
it reminds me of my own power to create
my own story and beauty no matter where
i am
all our stories are different and we all
express ourselves in different ways
and for me my home is a space where i
can truly allow myself
to be me
[Music]
we do have a little spare room and of
course a bathroom in this house however
it is very plain and uneventful so i
will not show you those rooms since
there are bare or still full of boxes
that are yet to be unpacked
so i ask your understanding that there
are certain nooks of the house that will
be kept private but that over time i
will be able to share more
[Music]
because tourism and general interest has
grown so drastically in this area
homes over the last few years have
become incredibly expensive
there's no way that my fiance and i
would have been able to get a house in
the forest here if it wasn't for the
kindness of his parents who moved here
long before it was such a hot spot
and were able to purchase this piece of
land and sell it to us for a price that
we could afford as we both work full
time
[Music]
luke is a surveyor in the area it is a
very physically demanding job especially
out here in the mountains
and since i as well work long hours it
is so nice to come home to a place that
feels simple and safe where we can
recharge and enjoy the company of so
many lovely pine trees
if you watch this channel you know that
i've lived in some unsafe apartments and
been in some relationships with people
who put me in danger
all those life experiences while
challenging also taught me that a sense
of safety
physically emotionally and spiritually
is an incredible feeling
after love perhaps it is the most
important thing we can imbue into our
space
[Music]
this corner of the house is currently
the plant nook but hopefully it will be
transformed into a personal library soon
luke has a lot of experience in woodwork
and construction and so he's making me
some customized bookshelves as a wedding
gift
[Music]
so yes yes before you say it i am
turning in my fairy wings the camera is
so shaky during these attempted
panoramic shots it utterly failed
believe it or not i truly thought the
camera was smooth by the time i drove
into town and saw it it was too dark to
refilm it
i appreciate your understanding i am
simply standing in the middle of the
room and poorly attempting to move in a
circle
[Music]
oh my gosh this looks so bad
thank you guys for being so patient with
me
[Music]
i already made a video about the
upstairs of the cottage and more or less
how it's decorated so i'll leave it for
another day and we'll link videos down
below that show it some more if you're
interested
currently this is my little makeshift
workstation for my etsy shop thank you
so much everyone who has supported my
art it really helps me keep this channel
running
and as a thank you again this week i
will be including an extra bookmark and
my usual quote card and sticker in each
order
thank you so so much i am so grateful
[Music]
my main inspirations for my space
definitely are fairy tales
and
folk lore and folk art
and there are a lot of movies that have
inspired me in the way that i decorate
as well as books and music and so
i will leave links to some of my
favorite music books and movies down
below
because i know that's something that has
interested people in the past and i
would like to share some of my favorites
in case they may become your favorites
as well
so i also encourage you to look in the
description bar down below because i
want to mention some incredible creators
who i've connected with
that have really inspired me in their
styles or in their art or just in their
way of looking at the world some that
come to mind are poems for the moon it's
a charming life parking on the
wild side i hope i get that word i hope
i get their name right i was recently
gifted some incredibly beautiful
handmade uh ceramics by a
artist on instagram that connected with
me that enjoys these videos and i wanted
to share her work too because it is
absolutely gorgeous i will leave all
links to these people down below please
check them out they're incredible and
creative with all that being said stay
tuned because each room is going to be
continually transformed throughout this
year as i keep working on it and getting
new ideas for paintings and finally get
some more basic pieces of furniture a
lot of our resources went to the down
payment of this house and just getting
the basic things put together and so now
that i am able to start little by little
decorating it's going to be a slower
process but extremely
rewarding to me because i always find
this process so calming and
just wonderful i hope the space inspires
you to reconsider the power of buying
things from unique places thrift shops
and antique shops and even resale shops
that there are so many incredible more
sustainably minded ways to decorate your
home that make it extra unique but of
course nothing is perfect none of us can
avoid buying new things most of the time
consider other ways to imbue that kind
of unique whimsy into a space that's one
of the reasons i usually
am unable to link
items from my home in videos because i
don't know where they're from
they are
i'm sure not one of a kind i'm sure
there's a lot of other very similar
things out there but i don't always know
the brand and i don't always know
exactly where something has come from be
that a flower pot
these were i think goodwill
and
i have no idea they say japan on the
bottom but that's as much as i know some
of the things that i did have to buy new
because i just couldn't find them
anywhere were rugs and curtains and some
little things like that and i will link
those down below in case you are looking
for something similar i hope you enjoyed
if you are a whimsical creative person
definitely
encourage yourself to express yourself
in your space you know i think when we
let go
about that fear about what other people
may think
um
we can really be free and you just
become more and more
embracing of just who you are and not
worry so much that
you know some people may take a double
take when they see flowers on your wall
but
that doesn't mean that they aren't
intrigued and
it's just very exciting to share this
all with you
and to share with you the continual
journey because i will be painting
murals
and all types of things and making the
space even more um eclectic i'm gonna
use the word eclectic yeah
i'm sending you wonderful dreams full of
pixie dust and i will see you soon
goodbye
[Music]
do
you